حزين من الشتا و الا
Sad from the winter or
حزين من الظما يا طير
sad from thirst ya bird
دخيل الريشتين اللي
by the two feathers that
تضفك حل عن عيني
lift thee, get away from my eyes
دخيل الما(ء) و ملح الما(ء) و حزن الما(ء) قبل ما تطير
by the water! the salt of the water!! and the sadness of the water!!! before you fly
تهيا للهبوب اللي تتصافق في شراييني
prepare for the winds that slap around in my veins
حزين من الشتا و الا
sad from the winter or
حزين من الظما يا طير
sad from the thirst ya bird
دخيل الريشتين اللي
by the two feathers that
تضفك حل عن عيني
lift you get away from my eyes
دخيل الما(ء) و ملح الما(ء) و حزن الما(ء) قبل ما تطير
by the water and salt of the water and sadness of the water before you fly
تهيا للهبوب اللي
prepare for the winds that
تتصافق في شراييني
slap around in my viens
دخيل الغصن و الظل الهزيل و هفهفة عصير
by the branch and the weak shadow and the wind of afternoon
دخيلك لا تشح بنجمتي و الليل ممسيني
please don't deprive my star as the night is saying hi
دخيل الغصن و الظل الهزيل و هفهفة عصير
by the branch and weak shadow and wind of afternoon
دخيلك لا تشح بنجمتي و الليل ممسيني
please don't deprive me my star as the night is saying hi
دخيل الغصن و الظل الهزيل و هفهفة عصير
by the branch and the weak shadow and the wind of afternoon
دخيلك لا تشح بنجمتي و الليل ممسيني
please don't deprive me my star as the night is saying hi
حزين من الشتا و الا
sad from the winter or
حزين من الظما يا طير
sad from thirst ya bird
دخيل الريشتين اللي
by the two feathers that
تضفك حل عن عيني
lift thee get away from mein eyes
ترفرف يا فقير الريش
you flap thy wings ya poor feathers
ضيقة و النهار قصير
of annoyance and the day is short
علامك كل ما ليل جناحك
whats up with you everytime your wing is at night
جيت ساريني
you came to me at night
أنا ما ني بخير و جيت يمي و انت ما انت بخير
i am not ok and you came next to and you are not okayyy
و انا يا طير فيّ من الحاجات اللي مكفيني
and i ya bird have enough things in me
ترفرف يا فقير الريش
you flap your wings ya poor feathers
ضيقة و النهار قصير
of annoyance and the day is short
علامك كل ما ليل
whats up with you everytime your wing is at night
جناحك جيت ساريني
you came to me at night
أنا ما ني بخير و جيت يمي و انت ما انت بخير
i am not ok and you came next to and you are not okayyy
و انا يا طير فيّ من الحاجات اللي مكفيني
and i ya bird have enough things in me
ترى لو شفت لي ظل و مهابة في عيون الغير
you see if you saw for me a shadow and fear in the eyes of others
ترا كل الزهاب اللي معي جرحي و سكيني
you see all the tools i have are my wound and knife
ترى لو شفت لي ظل و مهابة في عيون الغير
you see if you saw for me a shadow and fear in the eyes of others
ترى كل الزهاب اللي معي جرحي و سكيني
you see all the tools i have are my wound and knife
ترى لو شفت لي ظل و مهابة في عيون الغير
you see if you saw for me a shadow and fear in the eyes of others
ترى كل الزهاب اللي معي جرحي و سكيني
you see all the tools i have are my wound and knife